<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Bakio</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mapa">Map</string>
    <string name="image_button_description">Button with a tower as an image</string>
    <string name="reproducir">Play</string>
    <string name="pausar">Pause</string>
    <string name="exit_button_description">Exit button</string>
    <string name="corregir_button_desc">Correct answer</string>
    <string name="siguiente_button_desc">Go to the next question</string>
    <string name="volver_button_desc">Return to the start</string>
    <string name="siguiente_actividad">Next Activity</string>
    <string name="hola">Hello friends! Welcome to Bakio!</string>
    <string name="imagen_sonrisa">Welcome image with a smile</string>
    <string name="intro_expli">I am Lanper, the character of the Bakio festivities, and today I will guide you through its most important places and traditions. During the tour, we will play at each stop to make the visit more fun and educational. It will be an incredible experience!</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="reiniciar">Restart</string>
    <string name="mapa">Map</string>
    <string name="titu_arrastrar">ANARRU EGUNA</string>
    <string name="expli_arrastrar">Bakio’s Carnival stands out for its unique characters, such as Anarrua, the symbol of the celebration, and the gnomes that add mystery. Traditional dances like the Anarruen octocoa and rituals such as the trial and burning of Joseostu combine tradition, magic, and fun to ward off evil and celebrate the community.</string>
    <string name="jugar">Play</string>
    <string name="titu_bela">CROSSED SAILS AGAINST THE WIND</string>
    <string name="expli_bela">Years ago, pirates fought battles at sea, leaving behind destroyed and sunken ships. In Bakio, a pirate yacht sank in the harbor, later inspiring José Ramón Anda to create a blue sculpture representing the sea and that yacht. Even the Bakio rock evokes the shape of a yacht in honor of that story.</string>
    <string name="titu_gaztelu">San Juan de Gaztelugatxe</string>
    <string name="expli_gaztelu">The chapel of Gaztelugatxe, probably built in the 12th century, has witnessed sieges, looting, and attacks. Raiders and corsairs destroyed valuables and threw objects off the cliff.</string>
    <string name="expli_kahoot">Well, well… that’s all, and now, to wrap everything up, let\'s do a series of questions based on everything we\'ve learned!</string>
    <string name="titu_pelaio">SAN PELAIO HERMITAGE</string>
    <string name="expli_pelaio">The hermitage of San Pelaio in Bakio is one of the oldest Romanesque churches in Bizkaia. Built with thick stone walls, it has withstood the test of time and retains its original layout, although it has been restored. Its most notable feature is the apse with a window decorated with vegetal and geometric motifs, reflecting medieval art.</string>
    <string name="titu_lanper">LANPER</string>
    <string name="expli_lanper">In Bakio, the San Joan Doloza festivities, from August 28 to 31, feature Lanper, a symbolic lamp that participates in parades and events. The rest of the year, it rests at the town hall.</string>
    <string name="titu_txakolina">TXAKOLINA</string>
    <string name="expli_txakolina">Txakolí is a typical wine of the Basque Country, made from grapes grown in mountainous vineyards and stored in wooden barrels called kupelas. Bakio is home to several wineries and the Txakoli Museum, which tells its history and curiosities. It can only be enjoyed by those over 18 years old.</string>
    <string name="titu_martxitako">MATXITXAKO LIGHTHOUSE</string>
    <string name="expli_martxitako">The Matxitxako lighthouse, standing 20 meters tall and located 122 meters above sea level, emits light signals to guide ships and is visible from 30 nautical miles away. Originally, lighthouses were operated by keepers, but now most are automated thanks to modern technology. Today, fewer than 1,500 lighthouses remain in operation worldwide.</string>
    <string name="fin">END OF THE GAME</string>
    <string name="titu_act_gaztelu">Guess the correct answer</string>
    <string name="pregunta_gaztelu">How many steps does Doniene de Gaztelugatxe have?</string>
    <string name="pregunta_anterior">Previous question</string>
    <string name="siguiente_pregunta">Next question</string>
    <string name="comprobar_respuestas">Check answers</string>
    <string name="volver">Return</string>
    <string name="titu_final_resultados">Results</string>
    <string name="fin_del_juego_boton">End of the game</string>
    <string name="actividad_final_boton">Final Activity</string>
    <string name="titu_bienvenido_al_juego">Welcome to the Game!</string>
    <string name="titu_registro">Enter username and password</string>
    <string name="nombre_regis">Name</string>
    <string name="contra_regis">Password</string>
    <string name="registrarse_boton">Register</string>
    <string name="boton_corregi_resp">Correct</string>
    <string name="titu_act_pelaio">San Pelaio</string>
    <string name="titu_act_wally">FIND THE THREE TOWERS</string>
</resources>